Community Theater Journal, New York State; Collection ua950.015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
New York State Community Theater Journal Collection1999-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua950.015
1.0 cubic ft.
Collection is made up of the New York State Community Theater Journal.
Administrative History
The New York State Community Theater Journal was first published in December of 1960. It was a joint publication from SUNY Albany and the New York State Community Theater Association. The NYSCTA was a representative of local theater in the state until 1987 when it was combined with the New York State Theatre Festival Association.
The periodical was used as the newsletter for the Association, consisting of news for the group and its members, as well as local theater news. It would also include articles about theater history, treating this as an educational journal for those interested in theater.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the publication of the New York State Community Theater Journal dating from the years 1960 to 1971. Information on local productions as well as those taking part in them can be found in these volumes. There are some select volumes missing from the collection but the majority of the pieces are in the collection.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged chronologically.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Theater--New York (State); College Publications; UAlbany Reference Collections
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 1 Number 1, 1960 December (Volume 1)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 1 Number 2, 1961 March (Volume 1)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 1 Number 3, 1961 June (Volume 1)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 1 Number 4, 1961 September (Volume 1)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 2 Number 1, 1961 December (Volume 2)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 2 Number 2, 1962 March (Volume 2)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 2 Number 3, 1962 June (Volume 2)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 2 Number 4, 1962 September (Volume 2)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Index, 1960 September (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 1)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 3 Number 1, 1962 December (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 2)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 3 Number 2, 1962 March (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 3)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 3 Number 3, 1962 June (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 4)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 3 Number 4, 1962 September (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 5)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 4 Number 1, 1964 January (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 6)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 4 Number 2, 1964 April (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 7)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 4 Number 3, 1964 July (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 8)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 6 Number 1, 1966 January (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 9)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 6 Number 2, 1966 April (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 10)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 6 Number 3, 1966 July (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 11)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Special Issue, 1967 March (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 12)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral, 1967 October (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 13)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Special Issue, 1967 October (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 14)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 8 Number 1, 1968 January (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 15)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 8 Number 2, 1968 April (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 16)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 8 Number 3, 1968 July (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 17)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 8 Number 4, 1968 October (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 18)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 9 Number 1, 1969 January (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 19)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 9 Number 2, 1969 April (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 20)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 9 Number 3, 1970 January (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 21)
- New York State Community Theater Jounral Volume 10 Number 1, 1971 October (Box 1 (New York State Community Theater Journal Collectio), Folder 22)